

Hua Long Hai

Front-end Developer

Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

🕓 0925624469 | 🕲 longhai.hua1006@gmail.com | 📠 LinkedIn | 🖫 <u>GitHub</u>

Summary

I am a graduated student at UIT. I focus on studying and researching in the development of E-commerce websites. Additionally, I have over 1 year of experience working as a collaborative lecturer at Teky, teaching Web Development

With my knowledge of UI/UX design, I enjoy solving front-end problems and creating best user experience for users. I also spend time learning and practicing to become a better developer.

Education

University of Information Technology - VNUHCM

2020 - 2024

Bachelor of Science in Information System (GPA: 3.0 / 4.00).

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

Experience

TEKY HOLDINGS.,JSC.

Oct. 2022 - Present

Collaborative Lecturer.

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

- Teach students build static websites using HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- Teach students build e-commerce website using Wordpress.
- Evaluate students quality, report students progress for each course.
- · Contribute teaching materials for the Academic team.

ICSP Co.Ltd.

Oct. 2023 - Dec. 2023

Intern Developer.

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

- Design Web UI/UX and create prototype using Figma.
- Implement Web UI with responsive from Figma design using HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- Define and fix controller's bug of new user flow.
- Report task progress to mentor.
- Test and find error of website and mobile app using Selenium, manual.
- Create test case document to help agency developers fix bug.

Project

InTheOven (Personal project) - Front-end Developer

May. 2024 - July. 2024

- Overview: "In the Oven" is an online store for baked goods and beverages. Enjoy fresh breads, pastries, cookies, cakes, coffees, teas, and juices for a delightful experience.
- Technologies: ReactJS, Redux Toolkit, React-router-dom, React Hook Form, GitHub, Yup, Tailwind CSS, MUI.
- Responsibility: Design UX/UI all page and implement Web UI, responsive, implement routing using React router, manage global state using redux. Solving user experience problems.

Ovion (4 members) - Front-end Developer

Oct. 2022 - Dec. 2022

- Overview: Ovion is an online store dedicated to providing fashionable and comfortable shoes.
- Technologies: ReactJS, Redux, React-router-dom, React Hook Form, MongoDB, GitHub, Figma, Tailwind CSS, NodeJS.
- Responsibility:
 - Design UX/UI of additional page and implement Web UI, responsive, call API from back-end to render data.
 - Implement routing using React router, manage global state using redux.
 - o Collaborative with team to define website flow.

Technical skills

Programming Languages: JavaScript, Python.

Frameworks/Library: ReactJS, Redux, Redux Toolkit, React router, React Hook, Tailwind CSS, MUI, Boostrap.

Tools/Workflow: Github, MongoDB, Postman, Figma, StartUML, Notion, Trello, Canva, WordPress, Selenium.

Certificate: TOEIC RL (785/990), MOS Office.